altenergymag.com 2015-06-11

# Terms & Conditions - Privacy Policy | AltEnergyMag

The following privacy statement and refund policy applies to LJB Management Inc. and all of its subsidiaries and affiliates, including HomeToys.com, AltEnergyMag.com and AltEnergyMag.com. 

  * Personal Information
  * Third Parties
  * Log Files
  * Cookies
  * Update List
  * Miscellaneous Forms
  * Information Service
  * Removing or Changing Data
  * Consent to this Privacy Policy 
  * Refund Policy - Non Qualifying Paid Listings

#### Personal Information

This policy applies to all information submitted on this website. You may be asked to provide personal information so that you can register to receive information, receive catalogs, or order products. Your participation is voluntary and we will not require you to provide more information than is necessary to participate in any of our website's activities. In some instances, we may ask you questions on an aggregate basis (we don't identify you personally with the information) and such questions will be identified on the website. In all other instances, you should assume that we will track any information you provide on a personally identifiable basis.

#### Third Parties

LJB Management, Inc. may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about our users with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. We do not provide any identifiable personal information to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. For example, we may tell an advertising partner the number of catalog requests we receive from their publication, but we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Access by our employees and agents to your Personal Information is only on a need to know basis on the understanding that this is confidential business information.

Our intention is never to use or share personally identifiable information provided to us in ways that are different than the ways described above without also providing you with an opportunity to "unsubscribe" or prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### Log Files

IP addresses are gathered in the log files as with any standard Unix server. We use the log files to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Web site. 

#### Cookies 

Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer's hard drive when you visit a website. We use cookies to better tailor our site and our products to your interests and needs. Cookies may also be used to help speed up your future activities or to improve your user experience by remembering the information that you have already provided to us. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not voluntarily provided by you (i.e., during membership registration or a catalog request). The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most websites. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent so that you can flush them from your browser if you object to their presence.

Please note that you may not Log In to view restricted information unless your browser is set to accept cookies.

#### Update List 

Our subscription form requests users to give us their Name, Email address and some general demographic information. This information is not available to the public or any 3rd party. Monthly updates are sent by email to each subscriber. There may be additional email updates from time to time if the news is deemed to be important to the subscribers.

#### Miscellaneous Forms (Directory, Links, Software etc.)

Various forms request names, addresses etc. The information gathered is used to provide the services requested by the form. This information is not available to the public or any 3rd party.

#### Information Service

In the case of the Information Service ... the gathered data is forwarded to the companies from whom the reader has requested information. These companies may use that information as they see fit. LJB Management only provides the data to the companies that the reader requested the information from and it is not available to the public or any other 3rd party. 

#### Removing or Changing Data 

Readers may remove or change their information in our databases by requesting same. Email requests should be sent to [bobh@ljbmanagement.com](mailto:bobh@ljbmanagement.com)

#### Your Consent to this Privacy Policy 

By using this website, you signify your assent to the LJB Management, Inc. Company Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not use this site or submit any personally identifiable information.

#### Refunds for Non-Qualifying Paid Listings

Inappropriate or non site related paid listings will not be activated at the discretion of the editor. You will be notified by email of a disqualified listing within 48 hours and have the option of resubmitting a new listing or receiving a refund.
